Kevin Frank

COMPUTER ENGINEER

info@resumekraft.com 🔀

202-555-0120

Chicago, Illinois, US Q

linkedin.com/resumekraft in

SUMMARY

Graduate of computer engineering with more than 1 year of hands-on experience working across the full-stack of software development and as a data scientist. I've built a few projects by myself and I'm looking for a role where I can grow and learn from other experienced team members.

SKILLS

- Neural Networks
- Machine Learning
- Python
- Java
- C#
- Financial Analysis / Investments / Behavioral Finance
- JavaScript / Html / Css
- Django
- MongoDB
- REST APIs
- · Entity Framework
- ASP.Net MVC
- Specflow (Gherkin)
- · Git / GitHub / Bitbucket / JIRA

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Intern (Long-Term)

Innova IT Solutions May 2020 - Aug 2020

Worked as a full-stack web developer with .Net Core and Webix framework at two projects at the same time. Attended courses and gained certificates for Neural Networks and Deep Learning. Contributed to a document management system project.

Data Science Intern (Long-Term)

STM A.Ş (NATO-Secret level defence company), Sep 2019 - Dec 2019

Worked at the one of the biggest companies in defence industry as a data scientist and web developer in a cyber security project. Created a solution for multi-class text classification problem using SVM and Random Forest. Attended lectures and seminars about Data Science provided by STM-Academy. Worked on text summarization problem and provided a solution to the problem using machine learning.

Software Developer Intern (Long-Term)

ROKETSAN A.Ş. (NATO-Secret level defence company), Jan 2019 - Apr 2019

Worked at the one of the biggest companies in defence industry as a full-stack web developer using Asp.net MVC. Contributed integration from NHibernate to Entity Framework. Researched and prepared documentation about Elasticsearch for later use.

PROJECTS

Communica-p-tion (Capstone Project)

Developer, Team Member

- Developed Microsoft HoloLens and Android application providing assistance for hearing and visually impaired tourists. Implemented Speech to text, optical character recognition, and face detection. Used NLP for recommendation system. Implemented full-text search with Apache Lucene. Used Unity for android and Hololens.
- In this project, We worked with HAVELSAN A.Ş. with the use of Microsoft HoloLens.

Learning to Smell Challenge (AlCrowd)

Developer, Team Member

- Rank #13 out of 128 group of participants.
- · Implemented methods of machine learning for odor prediction from molecular

compounds that are represented with SMILES with a multi-label classification problem.

• Used RDKit Fingerprint and TensorFlow to solve this problem.

Maze Solver

Developer

• Implemented a maze solver with artificial intelligence search algorithms such as A* search and Breadth first search using heuristic functions.

Recipe Jungle

Developer, Team member

 Recipe Management System for both Android and Web users. Implemented add, delete, modify, Share, like, comment, notification features features for recipes that other users can see. Also implemented other user's recipes. Used Asp.NET CORE, C#, Javascript, Html, Css, Bootstrap, SQLite for Web Application and Java and Android studio for Android application.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

San Jose State University Sep 2016 - Dec 2020

(Full Scholarship) CGPA: 3.33/4.00

CERTIFICATIONStructuring Machine Learning Projects

- deeplearning.ai

Neural Networks and Deep Learning

- deeplearning.ai

Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter tuning, Regularization and Optimization

- deeplearning.ai

Deep Learning for Business

- Yonsei University

Al for Medical Diagnosis

- deeplearning.ai

Introduction to Machine Learning

- Global Al Hub

Behavioral Finance

- Duke University